Ace 2 suited, ace 3 suited; this is pretty much the best Omaha high low hand because what it gives you gives you the aces you can win the high if you catch another ace or two.
It gives you suited ace 2 and suited ace 3.
With these, you can pick up a high of a straight, you can pick up a high of a flush and you can pick up a high of a straight flush.
So you have a number of ways to win a high and also you have a number of ways to win the low.
What does that mean visually?
Well let's take a look at this board here that I laid out.
We got a board of Jack 10 8 3 and 5 and our opponent has played a rather another and for Omaha high low.
But played it none the less and managed to draw out on us and catch the high of a straight to a queen.
At last he does not win the low with his 5-2 and he doesn't even qualify for a low because he matches the 5.
We on the other hand have a low hand, we have 8, 5, 3, deuce, ace so we would win half of the pot.